{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777043997","data":{"timestamp":" 946777043997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777051638","data":{"timestamp":" 946777051638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777056015","data":{"timestamp":" 946777056015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777060284","data":{"timestamp":" 946777060284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777068625","data":{"timestamp":" 946777068625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777078712","data":{"timestamp":" 946777078712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777083467","data":{"timestamp":" 946777083466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777087166","data":{"timestamp":" 946777087166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777091062","data":{"timestamp":" 946777091062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777095238","data":{"timestamp":" 946777095238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777099296","data":{"timestamp":" 946777099296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777102844","data":{"timestamp":" 946777102844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777108890","data":{"timestamp":" 946777108889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777114553","data":{"timestamp":" 946777114553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777117777","data":{"timestamp":" 946777117777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777121613","data":{"timestamp":" 946777121613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777125893","data":{"timestamp":" 946777125893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777129484","data":{"timestamp":" 946777129484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777132877","data":{"timestamp":" 946777132877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777136570","data":{"timestamp":" 946777136570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777139958","data":{"timestamp":" 946777139958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777144799","data":{"timestamp":" 946777144799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777148066","data":{"timestamp":" 946777148066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777151290","data":{"timestamp":" 946777151290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777154413","data":{"timestamp":" 946777154413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777158029","data":{"timestamp":" 946777158029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777163814","data":{"timestamp":" 946777163813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777184541","data":{"timestamp":" 946777184541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 7293dee5-30d8-42bb-afc0-2bc835f92379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777204388","data":{"timestamp":" 946777204388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777204762","data":{"timestamp":" 946777204761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777205246","data":{"timestamp":" 946777205245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777205589","data":{"timestamp":" 946777205589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777206009","data":{"timestamp":" 946777206007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777206497","data":{"timestamp":" 946777206496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777206720","data":{"timestamp":" 946777206719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777209863","data":{"timestamp":" 946777209863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777209899","data":{"timestamp":" 946777209899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777210612","data":{"timestamp":" 946777210612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777211006","data":{"timestamp":" 946777211006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777211299","data":{"timestamp":" 946777211299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777211512","data":{"timestamp":" 946777211511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777211721","data":{"timestamp":" 946777211721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777212050","data":{"timestamp":" 946777212050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777212289","data":{"timestamp":" 946777212288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777215475","data":{"timestamp":" 946777215474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777215885","data":{"timestamp":" 946777215885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777216995","data":{"timestamp":" 946777216995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946777217056","data":{"timestamp":" 946777217056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_043707"," gameId":" 821ce360-73da-4988-a88c-aca5ad471d3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}